A live house?
ライブハウス？
Yeah, Yeah!
そう
An old friend of mine from back in middle school invited us to come and play a show there.
中学ん時の友達がさ
一緒に出ないかって誘ってくれたんだ
へ～
でも これ大晦日って書いてあるけど…
This says here that the show is on New Year's Eve.
That's only ten days from now.
あと10日しかないぞ
But we really don't have anything ready.
なんにも用意してませんよ
へ でもたのしそう
Aw, but it sounds like fun!
I'd really love to give it a shot!
私 出てみたいな
Me too!
だろ
Mm-hmm.
うん
I don't know if I can handle playing in front of a big crowd again...
でも また大勢の人の前に出るのは…
Mio! You know, if you keep talking like that, you're never gonna grow as a musician!
澪 そんなこと言ってたらいつまでたっても成長できないぞ
You look really cool when you play your bass, Mio.
ベース弾いてる澪ちゃん かっこいいよ
Well, then, let's decide it by majority rule.
じゃあ 多数決で決めよう
Who wants to pass on the show?
今回パスの人…
Ritsu-senpai, Yui-senpai, I'm sorry.
律先輩 唯先輩 すみません
Huh! Such impudence!
All those in favor of playing!
こしゃくな 梓
じゃ 出たい人～
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
はい はい はい
Yes!
はいッ
Mugi-senpai?
ムギ先輩？
But, Mugi, I thought you had a big trip plan for the end of the year.
ムギは年末年始は旅行じゃなかったのか
Yes, but an opportunity like this doesn't come along very often.
うん でもこんなにいい機会めったにないでしょ
And besides--
それに…
I really think it would be absolutely wonderful for all of us to play a big show together on the very last day of the year.
今年最後の日もみんなで演奏ができるなんて
すごく幸せじゃないかなって
Mugi...
ムギ…
She has a point...
確かにそのとおり
I can't disappoint Mugi-senpai.
ムギ先輩を不幸にできない
Umm...
あの…
We change our votes to "yes."
私たちも参加で
Sweet! That settles it, we're playing a show!
よーし！
じゃあ参加決定～
Yahoo!
やった～！
We're in it to win it!
やるからには優勝だぜ
And that is how we all decided to play our first show together at a real live house.
こうして 私たちの初のライブハウス参戦が決まったのでした
I'm so excited!
ドキドキです
CHATTING NOW
Chatting Now
ガチでカシマシ　Never Ending Girls' Talk
It's really noisy
Never Ending Girls' Talk
We can't wait until the bell
rings at the end of class
終業チャイムまで待てない
Even if we're late,
leaving early is a
遅刻はしても早退はNon Non Non!
No no!
精一杯Study After School
study
hard
We'll
after
School
ドキドキが止まんない　フルスロットルな脳内
Our hearts won't stop thumping
Our thoughts are going on full throttle
希望·欲望·煩悩　リボンかけて包装
Hope
Desire
Suffering
Wrap them all up with a ribbon
ネタどっさり持ち寄り　New　Type　Version打ち込み
We'll gather lots of data
and put it in a new type version
男子禁制のプリ帳　恋綴った日記帳
We have a photo album without guys
and a diary written with love
スカート丈2cm　詰めたら跳ぶよ
If we cut our skirts
by 2 centimeters,
we can fly
昨日より遠く　おとといよりオクターブ高く
Further than yesterday
We'll reach a higher octave
than the day before
Jumping
now
Jumping Now
ガチでウルワシ　Never Ending Girls' Life
It's beautiful
Never     Ending
Girls'       Life
日々マジ　ライブだし待ったなし
We're looking
forward
to the daily
concert
早起きしても早寝はNon Non Non!
Even if we
get up early,
going to bed
early is a
No no!
Shouting with all
目一杯Shouting　わっしょい
W
e've
got
Hooray
It's splendid
ガチでスバラシ　Never Ending Girls' Song
Never Ending
Girls' Song
午後ティータイムには持ってこい
The afternoon
tea  time
is perfect
Our unrequited
L
O
V
E
will be defeated
片思いでも玉砕でHere we go!
But here we go!
歌えばShining After School
We'll
sing
for
you
After school
He's so cute!
かわいい～
Christmas is just around the corner, isn't it?
もうすぐクリスマスだね
C'mon, let's go.
ほら 行くぞ
Coming!
は～い
So this is a live house, huh?
ここがライブハウスか
I'm nervous for some reason.
なんだか緊張するね
Y-Yeah...
う うん
Hey, now, don't sweat it!
大丈夫だって
Hello? Anybody here?
すみませ～ん
Just a minute!
は～い
Yes, can I help you?
はい いらっしゃい
Um, well...
あ あの
We've come to apply to play the big show!
出演 申し込みに来たんですけど
We're After-school Teatime!
「放課後ティータイム」です
Oh, I've heard good things about you.
ああ 話は聞いてるわ
Love Crisis' Maki-chan referred you, right?
「ラブ·クライシス」のマキちゃんの紹介ね
Love Crisis? Oh, man, They have a really cool name!
「ラブ·クライシス」 なんかかっこいい名前
Hey, Ritchan, doesn't our band name seem a little bit too warm and fuzzy compared to theirs?
ねぇ りっちゃん
私たちのバンド名 ちょっとほわわんとしすぎかな
After-school Teatime, huh?
What a cute name. I like it.
「放課後ティータイム」って なんだか かわいいバンド名ね
She complimented us on it!
あれ 褒められた？
Special:   Live House!
Fluffy time, fluffy time...
So, that's what we sound like...
こんな感じですけど…
うん じゃあ 参加申し込み書を書いてもらえる？
All right, then, would you mind filling out this application form?
Okay!
はいッ
Let's see... On the day of the show, you have to arrive at 1PM.
えっと 当日出演者は13時入りね
Wow, that's pretty early...
結構早いんですね
Because of rehearsals.
Each band will get 15 minutes.
リハやるから 各バンド15分で
Meeting at 3PM. Doors open at 4PM. Show starts at 5PM. Got it?
15時からミーティング
客入れが16時
開演は17時ね
Sure!
あ～ は はい
Also,
あと 当日持ち込みの機材だけど
あ あたしが忘れてもみんなが…
Even if I forget, I'm sure the guys will--
as for what gear you'll be bringing, you'll need to fill out a basic itemized list beforehand.
基本 何を持ってくるかの事前申告が必要だから
So this is a ticket for our show...
これがライブのチケットか
後で書いてね
You can fill that out later.
Wow, I guess you have to pay if you wanna be let in...
入場料払わないと入れないんだね
They're not listening!
聞いてね…
Come on, I'll show you around the club.
じゃ 中を案内するから
This is the dressing room.
ここが楽屋
Dressing room?!
楽屋！こ ここが…
Wow, this is?!
Excuse me, would it be all right if we put up a shop curtain?
あの のれん かけたりしていいですか
Sign: Sakuragaoka High / Afterschool Teatime
Come in!
まいど
That would be so cool, Mugi-chan!
かっこいいね ムギちゃん
Wouldn't it, though?
でしょでしょ
You know, all of the other bands will be using the room, too...
他のバンドの子たちも使うから…
And this door leads to the stage.
で この扉からステージに
Awesome!
すっげーな
Oh, look, there's even a disco ball!
ねぇ
ミラーボールもあるよ
You need to think about what sort of lighting setup you want for your numbers.
演奏中の照明のプランも考えておいてね
It needs to be all swirly and sparkly and shiny and fun!
もう グルングルンのピカッピカッのキラキラで
We're really going to be playing here, aren't we?
ここで演奏するんですね
It's exciting, isn't it?
ドキドキするわね
Don't burn yourself out yet.
まだ燃え尽きるなー
We look forward to having you for the show!
じゃ 本番よろしくね
Yes, thank you very much!
よろしくお願いしまーす
Huh? You're playing at a live house?
えッ ライブハウスに？
Yeah, we're on our way to have a meeting there up to this.
そう 今からその打ち合わせなんだ
Ah, that's amazing!
すごーい お姉ちゃん
So, we have a four-song set,
曲目は４曲か…
"Stapler," "Brush Pen," "Curry," and "Fuwa Fuwa Time."
「ホッチキス」に「ふでペン」、「カレー」、「ふわふわ」でいいよね…
あッ 何着て歌う？
What should we wear?
How about what we wore to our first School Festival?
１年目の学園祭で着たやつか
えッ あのフリフリの…
Those frilly things?
Don't worry, I'm sure Miss Yamanaka wouldn't mind making one for you!
あずにゃんの分もさわちゃん先生が作ってくれるよ
ええ～ッ
Miss Yamanaka made some other outfits for us, too...
でも　他にさわちゃんが作ってきたのって…
Nurse, school swimsuit, frilly Lolita...
スク水　白衣　ロリロリ…
…イヤですッ！
No way!
んー じゃあ 新しく作ってもらうか
Why don't we have her make something new, then.
あッ 変身して戦う感じの衣装は？
How about something like transforming fighter outfits?!
Oh, adorable! You mean like magical girls?
あッ かわいい
魔法少女とか？
Why not just wear our uniforms?
制服でいいんじゃないか
I vote for uniforms!
制服がいいです
That's a great idea!
あッ それがいいね
あッ そうだ
Oh, right!
Here! Tickets for you and Jun-chan.
はい これ 憂と純ちゃんの分
Come watch us play, okay?
２人で見に来てね
Commemorative tickets to my sister's first take show...
お姉ちゃんが初めてライブに出る記念のチケット…
It almost seems like a waste to use them.
なんかもったいなくて使えない
You can't get in if you don't.
使わないと入れないよ
Let's see, I still have to give one to Nodoka-chan.
あとは 和ちゃんにも渡さないと
Here, this is for you!
はい 和ちゃん
Wow, you're playing a live show?
へー ライブに出るんだ
That's amazing.
すごいわね
You'd better hurry and get all our autographs now before we make it really big!
今のうちに 私たちのサイン もらっといたほうがいいよ
Oh, that's okay, Yui.
え 別にいいわよ
えッ…
But I already made one for you...
もう書いてきたのに…
You jumped the gun.
気が早いな
In that case, I'll take it.
分かった もらっとく
Oh, thank you, Nodoka-chan!
ありがとう 和ちゃん
Let's see, now we need to give one to Miss Yamanaka.
あとは さわちゃん先生に渡してっと…
あ
There's a poster!
貼ってある
I can't believe we're gonna be in this show.
私たち これに出るんだね
うん
Wonder what other kinds of bands will be playing?
他にはどんな人たちが出るんだかなあ
Mio-senpai?
澪先輩ッ？
Mio's kinda shy, that's all.
澪 人見知りだからな
Sis! I'm gonna take a bath first, okay?
お姉ちゃん お風呂 先入るね
'Kay!
は～い
Geeta, let's do our best together tomorrow, okay?
ギー太 明日は一緒に頑張ろうね
I just know this is gonna be a lot of fun!
きっと すっごく楽しいよ
楽しみだよね
Have a great show!
お疲れ様でーす
Huh?
はい？
Will do!
どうもー
Do you think they play in one of the other bands or something?
なんだろう 出演バンドの子たちかな
No, I'm pretty sure that they're fans.
の ファンの子たちじゃない
はぁーッ、既にファンが？
We've got fans already?!
Hi, everyone!
こんにちは～
It's nice to meet you all!
よろしくお願いしま…
こ これは皆さん 手ごわそうな…
Everyone seems like they're really hardcore...
Hey there, how are you doing?
おはよ～ッす
How's it going?
おはよう
Nice to meet ya.
よろしく
They were nice and said hello!
ちゃんと挨拶してくれた
Yo, Ritchan!
りっちゃん
澪ちゃんも久しぶり
You, too, Mio, it's been forever!
Good to see you, Maki!
あ～ マキちゃん
Let me introduce you, guys.
みんな 紹介するね
This is my friend Maki, drummer for Love Crisis.
こちら「ラブ·クライシス」のドラムのマキちゃん
She's the one who sent us the invite to play!
今回 ライブに誘ってくれた
Nice to meet ya.
よろしくね
The pleasure's all ours!
こ こちらこそ！りっちゃんがいつもお世話になってますッ
Thank you for looking after our Ritchan!
うわ～ 澪さんだ！
It's Mio!
This is Aya, our bassist.
She's a big fan of yours, Mio.
うちのベースのアヤ
澪ちゃんの大ファンでさ
えッ？
You were completely awesome at the School Festival show!
学園祭でのライブ かっこよかったです
Oh, you came to see us play?
えッ 見に来てくれたんだ
Yeah, you're the one who came late!
あッ 遅れて来た人
I-I'm so sorry! I'm so sorry!
すみません すみません
It's okay, it was a fun show!
そんな 楽しいライブでした
Is she okay?
あの…
Sorry, it's 'cause we don't get complemented on our performances by strangers very often.
あッ ごめん
知らない人からライブを褒めてもらったことあんまりないから たぶん…
I think.
Well, that explains it.
そうなんだ
Oh, that's right!
あッ そうだ 今度私たちのライブ 是非見に来てください
Make sure you come see us at our next show, okay?
Our next one's gonna be a solo gig.
次は単独ライブなんだ
Goodness...
すごい
Oh, and have a CD!
よかったらＣＤも
It's homemade, but still...
手作りなんだけど
This is amazing!
すごいですね！
Gotta go! Talk to you later!
それじゃあ また後で
Sure!
うん
Their enthusiasm is on a whole other level...
なんか うちらと意気込みが違うな
Hey, you know, we really ought to have a logo or something like that, too, shouldn't we?
ねえねえ 私たちも なんかロゴマークとかあったらいいね
へ？
Let's see...
えーと…
えっとね こんなのとか
How about this one?
That's like for a hot spring!
それじゃ 温泉だ
It is?
あれ
Why don't you try adding a tea cup?
ティーカップも書いたらどう？
Like this?
こう？
おーッ まったりお茶するイイ感じ
It's like we're having a leisurely cup of tea!
All done!
できました
Draw one on these, too!
これにも書いて書いて
And on my keyboard!
私のキーボードにも
I want mine on my guitar case.
じゃ 私もこれに
I'd like one on my pick.
私もピックに
Great! we'll all be matching!
みんなでお揃いだね～
Okay, time to go to the meeting!
じゃ ミーティング始めまーす
あッ
うん
Oh, yeah!
よっしゃー！
Let's do it!
いくぞー
けいおん！
お～ 私たち２番目だ
We're gonna be the second band to play!
Second, huh?
２番かぁ…
Excuse me.
すいませーん
Here are your backstage passes.
これ バックステージパスです
あ ど どうも…
Thank you very much.
Yeah, thank you.
すみません
So where do you think we should stick these?
これ どこに貼ればいいの？
Oh, like that!
あれか
Amazing...
すごい…
They're like battle-hardened veterans of the show circuit.
ライブ重ねてきたツワモノだな
うん
And these will be the very first ones that we're gonna collect!
じゃあ 私たちはこれが１枚目だね
Yeah!
はいッ
Here.
At show time, you can't get back in here unless you have the pass stick somewhere on yourself.
イヤイヤ 当日は自分に貼らないと出入りできないから
あッ そうなんだ
Oh, yeah, you're right!
You're putting it there?!
そこに貼るか
What?
ほえ？
It's not a patch!
湿布か
え～？
It seems like I'm playing it safe...
なんか 無難な位置だなあ
あッ
Oh, right! Let's fill out our setup sheet!
それよか セッティングシート書こうぜ
へ～
L to R: Song Order | Original Performer | Backing Track | Song Tempo | Acoustics Requests
It's got spots for everything!
色々書くとこあるんだねえ
Well, we've got our song names and melodies, so that's okay, but...
まあ　曲名や曲調は決まってるからいいとして…
What's it mean by "lighting style"?
照明のイメージって？
Yeah, that's a really good question.
それなんだよな
What do you think we should put down?
どう書けばいいのかなあ
あッ
Wait, I'll be right back!
ちょっと行ってくる
Why did she head straight to the scariest-looking bunch?!
よりによって一番怖そうな所へ！
They wrote down stuff like "cheerful and happy" or "pop-style"!
「元気よく」とか「ポップな感じで」って書いてた
はは～
We'll go with something like that, then.
じゃあ うちもそんな感じで
Wait a second!
待って
Ours should... It should all be pink!
うちは…全部ピンクで！
All pink?!
ピンクですか？
We can't?
ダメ？
Well, we can go with a pink vibe for Fuwa Fuwa Time.
…じゃ 「ふわふわ時間」のサビはピンクで
あッ ミラーボールも
And let's use the disco ball!
Okay, we'll use it for the intros and solos.
じゃあ 前奏と間奏に使おうぜ
What else?
あとは…
It might be pretty cool to have them put a tight spotlight on me!
ズバッとあたしにピンスポット当ててもらってもいいかな
ズバッ！
Hey, why put the light only on you?!
なんで律先輩だけに
What we should do is have them light up each member of the band right as we're being introduced!
メンバー紹介の時に１人ずつ照明当ててもらいましょうよ
And on Geeta, too!
ギー太にもね
I don't want one on me!
私はいらないから
If the bassist trips, get a spot on her.
ベースが転んだらすかさずピンスポを…
I'm not gonna trip!
絶対転ばない！
What about "acoustics style"?
音響イメージはどうする？
Wait! Give me a sec!
待ってて
They wrote stuff like "Reverb on song 3," and "Both of the guitars" and "Boost the vocals to the max."
「３曲目 リバーブ下さい」とか「ボーカル目一杯下さい」とか書いてた
ああ じゃあ うちもそんな感じで
We'll write down stuff like that, then.
Where is it that we are supposed to do our banter?
ＭＣはどこに入れるんだろう
I'll go ask!
聞いて来る
They're done with theirs, so they said we could use it for reference if we want!
書き終わったから これ参考に持ってていいって
We're so sorry!
す すんません
Thank you, guys!
ありがとう～
She's friends with them already...
既に馴染んでる…
She can be a force to be reckoned with.
ある意味最強だな 唯は
We can use the other bands' rehearsals as reference for us, too.
他のバンドのリハも参考になるからな
あッ
Wow, they use a ton of effects...
すごい エフェクターいっぱい
They have a personal mic!
あッ マイマイクだ
I wonder how much one of those mics costs?
いくらぐらいするんだろうな
Look, look!
ねえねえ！
They sell tasty snacks!
お菓子も売ってるよ
Ritchan, they sell CDs!
あッ りっちゃん ＣＤが売ってるよ
Gosh, we don't have any merchandise to sell, huh, Mio-chan?
私たち売るものないね 澪ちゃん
あずにゃん 私たちもこれに写るのかな
Azu-nyan, do you think we'll ever be on one of these, too?
すごいね ムギちゃん！
This is amazing, Mugi-chan!
Come on, come on, come on...
T to B: Death Bang Bang Chickens / Afterschool Teatime / Cheeky Chicks / Black Thrill / Love Crisis
Look, it says "After-school Teatime" here! Check it out!
うわ～ 「放課後ティータイム様」だって 様！
Calm down, already, will you?
いいから 落ち着け！
Shall we have some tea?
お茶にしよっか
え～！
Mugi's a force to be reckoned with, too.
ムギもある意味最強だな
ほわ～ おいしいね
This is good...
This hits the spot!
やっぱこれだなあ
That smells good!
あッ いい香り
If you like, please feel free to join us for tea.
よかったらご一緒にお茶いかがですか
えッ
Well... If you insist.
じゃあ…遠慮なく
へぇ～ じゃあ 結構いろんなコンテストに出てるんだあ
So I guess you've been in a lot of contests, huh?
Yeah, but we haven't managed to win any, though.
なかなか入賞できないんだけどね
But we're going pro, so we're not giving up.
でも 絶対プロになりたいから
That's for sure. The instant you give up, it's all over.
そうだよね 諦めたら終わりだもん
I wanna keep playing music forever.
ずっと 音楽やってきたいし
Oh, wow...
すごい…
They're all in bands because they really wanna play music.
みんな 音楽がやりたくて バンドやってるんだな
It's kind of embarrassing that we said we were gonna play the Budokan, huh?
目指せ武道館って言ってたのが恥ずかしいね
Maybe it's thanks to Yui's spirit, and Mugi's grace, and everybody else that we can talk like this.
こんな話ができたのも
唯やムギ…みんなのおかげかも
みんな いつもちょっとずつ新しいドアを開いてくれる
We're always opening new doors for ourselves, little by little.
After-school Teatime! Please start your rehearsal!
「放課後ティータイム」さん
リハお願いしますッ
Oh, no! We got a little too calm down!
しまった！まったりしすぎた
W-What do I do first?!
んあッ まず何から…
Check your setting!
セッティングだろ！
O-Of course!
そ そうね！
Who are you talking to?!
誰に言ってんですか
Okay, whenever you're ready.
じゃあ お願いします
Right!
はい
E-Everybody ready?
じゅ… 準備ＯＫ？
Oh, yup!
いいーッす！
Yes!
はい！
Good to go!
だいじょーぶっ！
う うん
Okay, Um, then... We'll start with the second chorus from Fuwa Fuwa Time, all right?
じゃ じゃあ えーと…
４曲目「ふわふわ時間」ワンコーラスいきます
Yui! Sing!
唯 ボーカル
Ah, oops!
あッ し しまっ…
だい だいじょう…
Yui!
Mio-senpai!
澪先輩！
Calm down, everybody!
落ち着け みんな
Just relax.
落ち着いて
Hey, just take it again from the top, all right?
もう一回最初からでいいよー
Don't sweat it, you'll be fine!
大丈夫 大丈夫ー
You can do it!
頑張れー
We have to work hard so we don't make everybody else look bad!
みんなに迷惑かけないように ちゃんとやらなきゃ
This isn't just our show.
私たちだけのライブじゃない
So we have to relax and give it our best.
だから 落ち着いて頑張らなきゃ
After all, this door was just opened for us!
せっかく 新しいドアを開いたんだから
Well, it ought to be somewhere right around here.
確かこの辺りのはずだけど…
うん？これ…
あッ これみんなお客さん？
They're all here for the show?!
So many...
こんなに？
I wonder Big Sis would be okay?
お姉ちゃん 大丈夫かなあ
Ui!
憂～
Big Sis!
お姉ちゃん
Thank you for coming Ui and Nodoka-chan and Jun-chan.
和ちゃんも純ちゃんも来てくれてありがとう
Looks like there's gonna be a big crowd.
すごい盛況ですね
Check it out! My backstage pass!
見て見て バックステージパス
Aren't you the least bit nervous?
あんた 緊張しないの
Sure I am! That's why I'm eating snacks to help me unwind!
するよ～お菓子食べて緊張ほぐしてくる
Oh, right! We'll call out your names from the stage, okay?!
あッ そうだ ステージからみんなの名前呼ぶね
No, don't! That'll just make US nervous!
やめて 私たちが緊張するか…
See you later!
じゃあ また後で
She's fine. She is her usual self.
大丈夫 いつものお姉ちゃんだ
Oh, man, It took forever for me to pull out my old outfits...
昔の服探してたら 時間かかっちゃたわよ
お気に入りのうさちゃん抱いて今夜もオヤスミ
ふわふわタイム
ふとした仕草に今日もハートZUKI★ZUKI
Catherine!
キャサリン
さりげな笑顔を深読みしすぎてOver heat！
Janice! What are you doing here?!
ジョディッツ
いつか目にしたキミのマジ顔
あんたなんで
Well, I'm the manager here at the club!
ここのマネージャーやってんの
Oh, wow, It doesn't look like you've changed a single bit!
あんたちっとも変わらないわね
瞳閉じても浮かんでくるよ
Oh, I've changed a lot!
か…変わったわよ
夢でいいから二人だけのSweet time欲しいの
For one thing, I'm the teacher of those terrific girls playing up there.
だって 私…あの子たちの先生してるんだから
You are, huh?
そうか
あぁカミサマどうして
好きになるほどDream night  せつないの
とっておきのくまちゃん出したし
今夜は大丈夫かな？
Show's over!
終わった～
It sure is...
終わったなあ
Good job, ladies.
お疲れ様
あ～ さわちゃん先生
Miss Yamanaka!
You waited for us?
待っててくれたの？
Big Sis!
お姉ちゃん
Sis, you were very very good!
お姉ちゃん すごい良かったよ
Thanks a lot, Ui.
ありがとう
You guys really played your hearts out, didn't you?
本当 みんな頑張ってたわね
You looked great up there.
かっこよかったわよ
Thanks a lot!
ありがとう
お疲れ様です～
Look at that!
すごいな
Yeah!
はい
Yeah, but we had Nodoka-chan and Ui and the others waiting out here for us.
でも 私たちも和ちゃんとかみんな来てくれたよ
Thank you, guys!
ありがとう～
Yeah, thank you!
Let's play together again!
また 一緒にライブしよーッ
Thanks for all your help!
お世話になれました
Thank you very much!
ありがとう～
And good job!
お疲れ様
We'll invite you to play again!
また誘うからね
Have a great new year!
良いお年を～
I have a tiger bikini, too, so try it on!
ほら トラビキニもあるから 着てみて～
Absolutely not!
イヤです！
何で…
Why not?
What happened to the mood?
さっきの感動がッ！
All right, guys, I have New Year's noodles for everyone!
みなさん 年越しそばもありますよ
Those look great!
うまそう！
I feel bad about swarming you like this.
ごめんね 大勢で押しかけて
Oh, no, I don't mind at all. For one thing...
いえ 全然です
だって…
う～ま～
Yummy!
That happy look on her face is enough to make me happy.
あの顔が見られるだけで幸せですから～
I got the old maid again?
あッ またババだぞ…
さあ 残すところ今年もあと一分を切りました
This year now has just one minute remaining!
あ いよいよだな
Almost time...
Mio, what kind of year did you have?
澪 今年はどんな年だった？
It was packed full of great times. Thanks to all of you.
たくさん楽しいことがあったよ
みんなのおかげで
Thank you, Ritsu.
ありがとう
あ…
Oh, stop it, you're freaking me out!
よ よせやい 気持ちわりぃ
え… き 気持ちわりぃって…
What do you mean freaking you out?
Hey, the new year's about to begin, everybody!
おーい みんな もうすぐ年明けだぞ
They fell asleep!
って 寝てるし
Happy New Year, everybody!
明けまして おめでとうございま～す
Oh, it's the new year...
あッ 年明けた
Hey! What's the big idea, falling asleep at a time like this?!
ちょッ 肝心な時に寝てどうすんだよーッ
They're all exhausted. But that's part of being in the Light Music Club...
グダグダ…
ほら ムギ 唯 あずにゃん 起きるって 新しい年が来るってば ったくもう
Mugi! Yui! Wake up, darn it!
けど それも軽音部だよな
For the love of...
Wake up! C'mon!
起きて
ねぇ
C'mon, wake up, everyone!
ねぇ みんな起きて
What? What is it?
なんだ
Where am I?
ここどこ？
What time is it?
今何時ですか？
Let's go watch the first sunrise of the year! The first one!
初日の出見に行こう 初日の出
I'm too sleepy to go.
眠いからいいや
What's the big idea, sleeping at a time like this?!
もう こんな時に寝てどうするの
Like you're one to talk?
いや お前が言うか
We left Miss Yamanaka behind, think she'll be okay?
さわちゃん先生置いてきちゃったけど 大丈夫かなあ
Ui's with her. She'll be fine. There.
憂ちゃんもいるし 大丈夫だろ
It's lovely...
きれい
Isn't it, though?
でしょでしょ
This is my secret spot.
ここ穴場なんだ
Okay, then... Here goes.
それじゃあ えっと…
A Happy New Year to all my best friends!
明けましておめでとうございます
Happy New Year to you, Mio!
おめでとうございます
Hey, Azu-nyan, how long are you gonna keep those ears on?
ところであずにゃん それ いつまでつけてるの
にゃッ
なッ なんで誰も教えてくれないんですか
Why didn't anyone tell me I still had them on!
Sorry, sorry, they just looked so good on you.
ごみんごみん あんまり似合ってたもんで～
They're awfully cute.
すっごくかわいい
Azu-nyan, you should be more confident.
あずにゃん 自信持ちなよ
うぅ～
Oh, good grief...
ふぅ やれやれ…
Please
don't say
"you are
lazy,"
Please don't say「You are lazy」
だって本当はcrazy
because
I am
actually
crazy
白鳥たちはそう　見えないとこでバタ足するんです
The swans
are actually
kicking their legs
hard out
of sight
Being true and sincere
to my instincts,
I accept that I'll
be tossed around
本能に従順 忠実　翻弄も重々承知
The path
ahead looks bright
前途洋々だし…だからたまに休憩しちゃうんです
That's why I
take rests
sometimes
近道あればそれが王道　はしょれる翼もあれば上等
If there's a shortcut,
it's the easy way out
If I have wings to use, then it'll be the best
ヤバ 爪割れた　グルーで補修した
Crap, I broke a nail!
I'll fix it with glue
That's enough to give me
a sense of achievement
それだけでなんか達成感
大事なのは自分　かわいがること
What's important is to take good care of yourself
自分を愛さなきゃ　他人も愛せない
If you can't love yourself, then you can't love someone else
Please
don't
say
you
are
Please don't say「You are lazy」
because
you
are
actually
だって本当はcrazy
Capable
hawks
能ある鷹はそう　見えないとこにピック隠すんです
hide their picks
out of sight
I try to use my imagination,
想像に一生懸命　現実は絶体絶命
but reality is a bitch
I'm still just learning,
発展途中だし…だから不意にピッチ外れるんです
so I'll be out of pitch sometimes